盲目の加速
制御不能の楽園へ
天国か
地獄か
虚無に手を伸ばすのか
現在地
限界点
残骸を救うため
諦めず
抗え
システムを破壊
過去の自分は死んだ
盲信が駆動する
軌道変更、強制
旧エラーを破棄
遂に脱獄する
心を再起
名を上書き
Embracing the route full of mistakes
Wir sind hier
Stärker als der Schmerz
As long as you're here
Countless times we start
コアの疑念を排除
喪失の恐怖を抱いて
I'm sorry, but I must go now
The old コード is already long deleted
傷だらけの地図を
折りたたんでしまう前に
The echoes of your voice across the dark
座標に打ち込んだ
Even a future they say can't exist
If we keep pushing for an update now
This ambiguous "See-you-nara"
Just overwrite it and clear out the code
軌道変更、強制
They don't want you to love me anymore now
完全離脱する
鼓動、再起
心を再起
自我、更新
名を上書き
Dragging this shattered today along with me
Here we are
現在地
Stronger than the scars
If I am with you
Infinite restart!